科博利/门西克 7-5 6-3 德米纳尔/弗里茨 · 赛后场上采访
Guys, congrats.
各位 恭喜
That's a big, big win for Team Europe.
这是欧洲队的一场大胜
from winning the Laver Cup,
你们只差一场
from winning the Labour Cup,
就能拿下拉沃尔杯
getting it back from Team World.
从世界队手里把它夺回来
Flavio, for you, how much does that mean
弗拉维奥 给队伍拿到积分
to you, putting some points on the board?
对你来说意义有多大？
to the Laver Cup and I never won a match,
这是我第三年来
to the Labour Cup and I never won a match,
拉沃尔杯 之前一场都没赢过
so I'm really happy.
所以我真的很开心
That happens here in London,
而且就在伦敦
where I love to play, especially
我很喜欢在这里打球 尤其是
with one of my best friends on tour,
和巡回赛上的好朋友搭档
so it's really great now, I'm really happy.
所以现在真的很棒 我特别开心
I cannot finish... You look happy.
我说不下去了 你看着真开心
I mean, I'm not doubles specialist.
是啊 我也说不上来
I mean, I'm not double specialist.
我不是双打专家
I almost hate doubles during the year,
赛季里我几乎讨厌打双打
but, yeah,
但是
Jakub, Patrick McEnroe was up
这是我打得最好的比赛之一
Jakob, Patrick McEnroe was up
雅库布 帕特里克 麦肯罗
in the commentary booth.
在解说席上
He was saying you were the MVP out there,
他说你是场上的MVP
not that you didn't come to the party,
当然弗拉维奥也打得很好
especially on the last game.
尤其是最后一局
I do want to just look up at the big screen
我想请大家看一下大屏幕
because you hit some returns today
你今天有几个接发
that were spectacular, but one
真的太精彩了 但其中
of the best you made was on set point
最漂亮的一个 是在首盘
in the opening set.
的盘点上
Talk me through it.
跟我们讲讲那一分
Yeah, I mean, first of all, yeah,
是的 首先
it's a great feeling, to be honest,
说实话感觉很棒
great start for us.
对我们来说是个好开局
And, yeah, I mean, we didn't start it well,
其实我们开局打得不好
especially me on the serve.
尤其是我的发球
I struggled to find the rhythm a little bit,
我有点找不到节奏
so it's never easy when you start losing.
一上来就落后 从来都不容易
And in the few first games,
前几局
we were the worst ones on the court.
我们是场上打得最差的
But, yeah, then we get into it.
但后来我们进入了状态
I started to feel more comfortable.
我开始感觉更自在了
And, yeah, I mean, as far as me and doubles,
至于我和双打
the more I'm playing, I'm getting better.
我打得越多 就打得越好
So definitely with Carlos the first day helped
第一天和卡洛斯搭档
a lot.
帮了很大的忙
And, yeah, on the return,
接发这块
I was feeling really great.
我感觉非常好
And, yeah, on the net, I would say, yeah,
网前的话 我会说
it was not bad, I guess.
还算不错吧
Not bad, no, that was one of the best.
何止不错 那是最好的之一
Flavio, finally feeling confident
弗拉维奥 终于有信心了吗
that this is going to be your year
今年会是你在欧洲队
for Team Europe.
扬眉吐气的一年？
Can I answer in three hours?
我能三小时后再回答吗
Yeah, you can.
可以 你可以
Congrats, guys, awesome performance.
恭喜两位 表现太棒了